{
  "FCQuestionBank": [
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the main character in the game?",
      "answer": "Brian"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the base name?",
      "answer": "The Legend of Zelda"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the best NCO?",
      "answer": "Brian"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the worst NCO?",
      "answer": "Dav"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many teeth you got?",
      "answer": "abouuut 3"
    },
    {
      "question": "Coolest part on being in the mil?",
      "answer": "the end"
    },
    {
      "question": "Wrorst part of the mil?",
      "answer": "the mid/end"
    },
    {
      "question": "What do you do if someone robs the BX?",
      "answer": "CHootem"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why do you have a sword?",
      "answer": "because I'm a hero"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the game?",
      "answer": "Zelda"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many cats you got?",
      "answer": "Bout 5"
    },
    {
      "question": "Where are we?",
      "answer": "Florida"
    },
    {
      "question": "What country?",
      "answer": "USA"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whos the Pres?",
      "answer": "Joe"
    },
    {
      "question": "Whos the VP?",
      "answer": "Dav"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why is CSS closed half the day?",
      "answer": "CDC's"
    },
    {
      "question": "Why are the Supra Coders cool?",
      "answer": "we aren't"
    },
    {
      "question": "Best SEC Football Team?",
      "answer": "University of Georgia"
    },
    {
      "question": "Worst SEC Football Team?",
      "answer": "University of Florida"
    },
    {
      "question": "Mac or PC?",
      "answer": "Mac"
    },
    {
      "question": "Boats or Cars?",
      "answer": "Who cares"
    },
    {
      "question": "Minimal Posting?",
      "answer": "66"
    },
    {
      "question": "Hardest job at Patrick?",
      "answer": "Elderly caretaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "Second hardest job at Patrick?",
      "answer": "Staying awake on mids"
    },
    {
      "question": "Best shred?",
      "answer": "K9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Worst shred?",
      "answer": "the b people"
    },
    {
      "question": "Size of the base?",
      "answer": "6mil Miles"
    },
    {
      "question": "How much is unguarded?",
      "answer": "all of it"
    },
    {
      "question": "Best hair in the unit?",
      "answer": "Veon"
    },
    {
      "question": "Worst hair in the unit?",
      "answer": "again...Dav"
    }
  ]
}